And so I ended up in an abandoned place.
It must.
You're wondering how I ended up here,
right?
Then I woke up 1 normal day.
This is my mobile dog project.
This is the guy's mobile dog project.
Bro can't,
no bro,.
I put my truffles in a store here to do a replacement that the woman called me,
are you tuned?
I could put the truffles on a tattoo bottle.
Hey Carol,
can you come in?
This is Dudu.
And then again,
did you leave the truffles there,
so where?
And suddenly it started to give me a headache,
a weakness
and I said,
brother,
you know what,
man,
I'm going to stop everything and
dedicate myself to making a bed in the Chevette.
Then I got some boards that I got from Vitor.
Who is the barber.
Like it's really crazy.
Sometimes we think we don't have the opportunity,
but in fact we have to create all this ourselves.
When I seek to be a more interesting,
less self-interested person.
Doors open and here I am.
Day twenty-eight making progress.
Maybe this isn't your lifelong dream,
nor mine.
But sometimes we need to leave point a to go to point b.
It's really God, right,
bro?
With back pain,
interfering with a lot of things.
The gas station manager arrived and said,
"Brother,
it's in the right place."
You can't stay for that long,
but I believe you can get some work done.
Sleep there, father.
Sleep there.
There's 1 bathroom,
there's 1 more key here before locking.
You test, huh?
Peru is not there yet,
but I took a bath there.
It's already fine
key to the castle today.
Having a headache with a bunch of stuff instead of sleeping in the chevas,
I'm going to sleep there.
Yes,
share this moment with you.
Hand oh my god,
face,
what a scare,
man.
Broke the box.